{
    "id": "3c65f431bc234129a8b0998fe8264ae7",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She was booked for driving at ………………………  110 miles per hour.",
            "description": "We use over, not above, to talk about ages and speeds.",
            "answers": [
                "above",
                "over",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "efa3e696708a44c2a471a986a4c569d3"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is ……………………… on his uncle for his educational expenses.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "dependent",
                "depending",
                "depend"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "446e5c14c6084b028e4e497ce0a5eb16"
        },
        {
            "question": "You can eat ………………………… in my restaurant whenever you want.",
            "description": "The adverb free means without payment freely means without restriction.",
            "answers": [
                "free",
                "freely"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b6292f1e82cc4854805dd86f2e8b402c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Under no circumstances  ............................  in the bar.",
            "description": "When the clause begins with a negative expression, we use an inverted word order. ",
            "answers": [
                "children are allowed",
                "are children allowed",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9acbfc467e4044bebbb5c45cfbb7cf7d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Britain ................................... as a land of law and order.",
            "description": "We need a passive verb here.",
            "answers": [
                "has long known",
                "has long been known"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e637acc367674777bc9d5c54cb463371"
        },
        {
            "question": "He wrote his first book after ............................. from Africa.",
            "description": "It should be returning or he returned.",
            "answers": [
                "returning",
                "returned",
                "he returned"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b417ceafed5d41b9a5e879352b61592a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I expected to fail the exam, but I passed ................................",
            "description": "After all means 'contrary to what was expected'.",
            "answers": [
                "at all",
                "after all"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4e09f28690984c0b8446b79bca7c3b35"
        },
        {
            "question": "When I was ................................ I was working.",
            "description": "When I was your age (the structure is/are/was + … age is used without a preposition) ",
            "answers": [
                "your age",
                "at your age",
                "of your age"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3405747c1820462a89e64c98e4fb97e4"
        },
        {
            "question": "All Indian ............................... suffered from white settlement in America.",
            "description": "We use a plural noun after all. ",
            "answers": [
                "tribe",
                "tribes"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1bf5a68851254e9a9094cac7cb9c1597"
        },
        {
            "question": "We do not allow people ................................. in the kitchen.",
            "description": "Allow is followed by an infinitive with to.",
            "answers": [
                "smoke",
                "to smoke",
                "smoking"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a6e41504cffc4571a4857afc844d034c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Alice is not free on the 15th.  We will have to find an ................................. date for the meeting.",
            "description": "Alternative means different.",
            "answers": [
                "alternate",
                "alternative"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6aebaee66f2b4080a58b27265ff05738"
        },
        {
            "question": "Her feet were sore because her shoes .............................. badly.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "fitted",
                "were fitted",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "80182ef375c748ebb8f1de4dd1dceeae"
        }
    ]
}